All hail the king.
Kong: Skull Island is a action, adventure, fantasy
film directed by Jordan Vogt-Roberts.
Explore the mysterious and dangerous home of the king of the apes as a team of
explorers ventures deep inside the treacherous, primordial island.
Captain James Conrad, played by Tom Hiddleston.
Lieutenant Colonel Preston Packard, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Bill Randa, played by John Goodman.
Mason Weaver, played by Brie Larson.
San Lin, played by Jing Tian.
Maj. Jack Chapman / Kong Mo-Cap Services, played by Toby Kebbell.
Kong: Skull Island is a 2017 American monster film
directed by Jordan Vogt-Roberts.
It is a reboot of the King Kong franchise and the
second film in the Monsterverse franchise.
The film stars Tom Hiddleston, Samuel L.
Jackson, John Goodman, Brie Larson, Jing Tian, Toby Kebbell, John Ortiz, Corey Hawkins, Jason Mitchell,
Shea Whigham, Thomas Mann, Eugene Cordero, Marc Evan Jackson, Terry Notary, and John C.
In the film, a team of scientists and Vietnam War soldiers in the year 1973 travel to the uncharted
Skull Island and encounter many of the island's monsters, including the mighty Kong.
The film was announced in July 2014 at San Diego Comic-Con, and
Vogt-Roberts was announced as the director in September 2014.
The project initially began at Universal Pictures as an
origin story but was later moved to Warner Bros.
to develop a shared cinematic universe featuring Godzilla and Kong.
Principal photography began in October 2015 in Hawaii and various
locations around Vietnam and ended in March 2016.
Kong: Skull Island was theatrically released on March 10, 2017, by Warner Bros.
Pictures, to generally positive reviews from critics.
It was a box office success, grossing $569 million against a $185 million budget, and
received a nomination for Best Visual Effects at the 90th Academy Awards.
A sequel, Godzilla vs.
Kong, was released in 2021, and an animated series,
Skull Island was released in 2023.
The film explores themes of vietnam veteran, island, monster, 1970s, expedition.
The tone is thought_provoking.